Jhaal,
so let's know how to print
or email the oil. First of all,
click on the insurance option and click on this track, the
policy number is like this. On
clicking on this policy, you will
see all the information of the policy.
Click on this button here.
On clicking the next button, an
OTP will come on the customer's registered number. Enter this OTP.
After a successful notification, the two-wheeler
insurance policy will be
downloaded as soon as you click on subscribe in this way.
You will print it and through this you
can give
this important information to the customer.
We will give a certificate of insurance
only to the customer and that too
after the situation is very sensitive, that is
why we take customer satisfaction,
so you will never share this with anyone. In
this way, you can
start a two-wheeler policy for the customer. Thank you
Jhaal.